FERNANDA ALDERETES

QA ENGINEER

I am a detail-oriented software development and quality assurance professional, with a curious mindset, a strong sense of teamwork and a friendly personality.

I have experience testing web and mobile applications and enjoy coding front-end projects in my spare time.



Address: Gruttolaan 8, 6005LN Weert

Phone: +31 6 24259453

Website: https://feralderetes-portfolio.netlify.app

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Vimcar Berlin I Germany

QA Automation Engineer | Sep 2023 - Jun 2024

Provided automation testing frameworks for web and mobile applications. Collaborated closely with the development teams to analyse and design a test strategy.

Quality Assurance Tester | Sep 2021 - Aug 2023

Created, executed and maintained manual test plans for web and mobile applications in the fleet management industry. Created and maintained selected automated E2E test cases.

QA Tester (freelancer) | Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

Created, executed and maintained manual test plans for web applications in the fleet management industry.

Sovos

Tucumán I Argentina

Quality Assurance Engineer II | Nov 2019 - Mar 2021

Designed, created and executed manual test plans for a web application in the tax regulation industry.

Created and maintained automated tests on various platforms. Provided on-call support during production releases and onboarding process for new hires.

Quality Assurance Engineer | Jul 2016 - Apr 2018

Created, executed and maintained manual test cases, bug reports and regression testing plans for a desktop and a web application in the tax regulation industry.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineer



National University of Tucumán - 2015

Recognised by the German Central Office for Foreign Education (ZAB) with the following evaluation:

"The foreign degree corresponds to a German university degree. In terms of level, it is to be classified between the Bachelor's and Master's levels."

SKILLS

- JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Java.
- Cypress, Selenium, Appium, Robot.
- Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ, Android Studio, Appium Inspector, Postman.
- JIRA, Github, Bitbucket, Jenkins, Bitrise, PractiTest, Zephyr for JIRA.
- SQL, Oracle SQL Developer.

LANGUAGES

- **Spanish**: Mother Tongue
- English: C1+ Level | Cambridge First Certificate in English, 2016, Grade: A (184/190)
- German: B1 Level | Goethe Zertifikat A2, 2017, Grade: 84/100
- Dutch: A2+ Level | DUO Basisexamen Inburgering, 2024, Grade: 10/10

HOBBIES

Cycling

Cooking \





